THE CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
이 드라마의 등장인물, 조직, 사건은 허구입니다.
Bloody hell!
이런 젠장!
Kill her!
그녀를 죽여라!
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Go ahead, kill him!
어서 그를 죽여라!
Damned!
저주 받은!
Find out what Jung Gicheul is up to
정기철이 무엇을 하는지 알아보세요
and where he goes with whom.
그리고 그는 누구와 어디로 가는지.
Keep us informed about it.
이에 대해 계속 알려주세요.
Dirt pigs!
더러운 돼지들!
Damn son of a bitch!
빌어먹을 개자식아!
You motherfuckers!
이 개자식들아!
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Hyeok is in the emergency room.
혁이가 응급실에 있어요.
I can't go fishing tomorrow.
내일은 낚시하러 갈 수 없어요.
You two go alone.
둘이서 혼자 가세요.
Hi, Boss.
안녕하세요, 보스.
I have a flat tire and am stuck.
타이어가 펑크나서 막혔어요.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Can you move on already?
벌써 진행할 수 있나요?
What are you fucking doing?
씨발 뭐하는거야?
Young Gicheul.
영기철.
You Hurensohn!
휴렌손이여!
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Do I look like a sneaky traitor, you son of a bitch?
내가 교활한 배신자로 보이느냐 , 이 개자식아?
Seung Ho.
승호
Get in quickly.
빨리 들어가세요.
You shit!
젠장!
Damned!
저주 받은!
Seung Ho.
승호
Kwon Seungho!
권승호!
Come on. Wake up.
어서 해봐요. 깨우다.
Seungho, stay with me.
승호야, 내 옆에 있어줘.
Go ahead!
계속하세요!
THE WORST OF EVIL
최악의 악
OPERATION
작업
-We need a lot of bandages. -Yes, doctor.
- 붕대가 많이 필요해요. - 네, 박사님.
-It's bleeding a lot. -Yes.
-피가 많이 나네요. -예.
-Do not touch the wound. -OK.
- 상처를 만지지 마세요. -좋아요.
-Mortgage. - Ok.
-저당. - 좋아요.
OPERATION
작업
Something happened on the way to the port.
항구로 가는 길에 무슨 일이 일어났습니다.
I am fully responsible.
나는 전적으로 책임이 있습니다.
Was that China, boss?
중국이었나요, 보스?
The Japanese should also be called.
일본인도 불러야합니다.
Wait outside.
밖에서 기다리세요.
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
Chief Seo.
서 실장님.
You know who knew besides the three of us
우리 셋 외에 누가 알았는지 알잖아
that I went fishing, right?
내가 낚시하러 갔다고, 그렇지?
Yes, Sir.
알겠습니다.
Heesung, Jungbae, Kyungjin, Byungwoo.
희성, 정배, 경진, 병우.
Find out who is in cahoots with Jaegeon.
재건과 공모한 사람이 누구인지 알아보세요 .
You're the only one I can trust.
내가 믿을 수 있는 사람은 당신뿐이에요 .
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
Hallo.
어이.
Were you recently called by a Mercedes with a flat tire?
최근 타이어 펑크로 인해 메르세데스로부터 전화를 받은 적이 있습니까 ?
Ah, that one.
아, 그거요.
I'm there,
내가 거기있어,
and the guy was totally unfriendly and just pushed.
그 사람은 완전 불친절하고 그냥 밀어붙였거든요.
There he is.
저기 있어요.
Must have driven very aggressively.
매우 공격적으로 운전했을 것입니다.
An unusual crack.
특이한 균열.
Is Seungho okay?
승호는 괜찮아?
Is Gicheul still in the hospital?
기철이는 아직 병원에 있나요?
And.
그리고.
These pigs will pay for it.
이 돼지들은 그 대가를 치를 것이다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
I was in the office the whole time that day.
나는 그날 내내 사무실에 있었습니다.
I watched a video with him,
그 사람과 함께 영상을 봤는데,
and that night we had a drink in his bar.
그날 밤 우리는 그의 바에서 술을 마셨습니다.
Before that we played pool.
그 전에는 당구를 쳤어요.
Exactly. We also went to a pool hall.
정확히. 우리도 당구장에 갔다.
Dont move. Hold still.
움직이지 마세요. 가만히 있어라.
I'll get help.
도움을 받을게요.
Captain Seok talks to the doctors.
석 선장이 의사들과 이야기를 나누고 있다.
-Worry... -You are irresponsible.
-걱정... -당신은 무책임해요.
They knew about the turf war with Song Donghyuk's gang.
그들은 송동혁 일당과의 영역 다툼을 알고 있었다 .
Did he really have to be alone there?
그는 정말로 거기에 혼자 있어야만 했나요?
Couldn't you take any precautions?
아무런 예방조치도 취하지 못하셨나요?
Have local support available?
현지 지원이 가능한가요?
We cannot predict every scenario.
우리는 모든 시나리오를 예측할 수 없습니다.
It is normal for unexpected situations to arise.
예상치 못한 상황이 발생하는 것은 정상입니다 .
And you want to go through with it after everything that's happened.
그리고 당신은 일어난 모든 일을 겪고 싶어합니다 .
Did it help Junmo in any way...
준모에게 조금이라도 도움이 됐나요...
... that I met Jung Gicheul?
...정기철을 만났다고?
If so, I want to help more actively.
그렇다면 좀 더 적극적으로 돕고 싶습니다.
If I can get my husband out of there unharmed,
남편을 무사히 구출할 수 있다면 ,
I meet Jung Gicheul and play along.
정기철을 만나서 같이 놀아요.
Anything to end this crazy operation quickly!
이 미친 작전을 빨리 끝내려면 뭐든지 하세요 !
That was the second time you saved my life.
당신이 내 생명을 구한 것은 그게 두 번째였습니다 .
I trust you now.
나는 지금 당신을 신뢰합니다.
Boss.
사장.
If so,
그렇다면,
can I have a cigarette?
담배 좀 피워도 될까요?
No product for us?
우리에게 맞는 제품이 없나요?
We didn't even meet the Korean captain.
우리는 한국 선장을 만나지도 못했습니다 .
No news from them?
그들에게서는 소식이 없나요?
No. His phone is turned off.
아뇨. 그 사람 전화기는 꺼져 있어요.
The payment was in advance, right?
결제는 선불이었죠?
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
Tried to reach her.
그녀에게 연락을 시도했습니다.
Because of the fishing trip...
낚시여행 때문에..
Are you really going fishing?
정말 낚시하러 가시나요?
Middle of the night?
한밤중?
At least the sailing part, yes.
적어도 항해 부분은 그렇습니다.
For what?
무엇을 위해?
After all that , I have a right to know.
결국 나에게는 알 권리가 있습니다.
Is it some kind of smuggling at sea?
일종의 바다 밀수인가요?
Everything in its time.
모든 것이 제때에 이루어집니다.
Found out what?
무엇을 알아냈나요?
Not yet, sir.
아직은 아닙니다.
I think I know who it is.
나는 그것이 누구인지 알 것 같아요.
Who is it, sir?
누구세요?
Send everyone back to Seoul.
모두 서울로 돌려보내세요.
They are supposed to gather at the office at 9:00 p.m.
그들은 오후 9시에 사무실에 모이기로 되어 있습니다.
Every single one.
하나하나.
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
And first tell them
그리고 먼저 그들에게 말해요
we would know who sold our gang to Jaegeon.
누가 우리 갱단을 재건에게 팔았는지 알 수 있을 겁니다.
And that I will punish the rat in front of everyone.
그리고 모두가 보는 앞에서 쥐를 처벌하겠다고요.
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
Bon Voyage. See you there.
본보야지. 거기서 보자.
JEIL HOSPITAL
제일병원
Moment. I have a question.
순간. 질문이 있습니다.
How are the guys who got shot doing?
총 맞은 사람들은 잘 지내나요 ?
They're all alive, don't worry.
다들 살아 있으니 걱정하지 마세요.
Instead, worry about yourself.
대신 자신에 대해 걱정하십시오.
Give me the key.
열쇠를 주세요.
Boss.
사장.
INTERNATIONAL, JAPAN
국제, 일본
-Hello. -You son of a bitch.
-안녕하세요. - 개자식아.
You dare to ignore our call?
감히 우리의 부름을 무시하는 겁니까 ?
Do you think we can't find you with our money?
우리 돈으로는 당신을 찾을 수 없을 것 같나요 ?
Do you think that?
그렇게 생각하시나요?
It's me.
나야.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
On the way to the sea
바다로 가는 길
Song Donghyuk's men attacked us.
송동혁 부하들이 우리를 공격했어요.
One of us almost died.
우리 중 한 명이 거의 죽을 뻔했어요.
An ambush?
매복?
That means they knew
즉 그들은 알고 있었다는 뜻이다
which route you would take.
어떤 경로를 택할지.
I also just noticed that I was being watched.
나는 또한 내가 감시당하고 있다는 것을 방금 알아차렸습니다.
There must be a rat
쥐가 있어야지
under your command.
당신의 명령에 따라.
Do you have anything to say about that?
그것에 대해 할 말씀이 있으신가요?
No.
아니요.
Either way, you are responsible for what happened.
어느 쪽이든 일어난 일에 대한 책임은 당신에게 있습니다.
What do we do?
우리는 무엇을해야합니까?
Start the car!
차를 시작하세요!
So really.
정말요.
Hey.
여기요.
Is not it ...
안 그래 ...
... really tight in here for you?
... 정말 여기 꽉 찼나요?
You can make yourself comfortable.
편안하게 지내실 수 있습니다.
Do you want to emulate Chow Yun-fat or what?
주윤발을 닮고 싶나요 ?
Wherever you go, there is war.
어디를 가든지 전쟁이 있습니다.
But somehow you never die doing it.
하지만 어쨌든 당신은 그것을 하면서 결코 죽지 않습니다.
Just like in A Better Tomorrow.
더 나은 내일(A Better Tomorrow)에서도 마찬가지입니다.
Man, Chow Yung-fat is so cool.
아, 주영발님 정말 멋있어요.
It would have been perfect with sticks.
스틱이 있었으면 완벽했을 텐데.
You probably fought like that too.
아마 당신도 그렇게 싸웠을 겁니다.
Total irre.
총 irre.
RASTHOF JINJONG
라스트호프 진종
I'm going to the bathroom.
나는 화장실에 갈거야.
Ok.
좋아요.
It seems you have to too.
당신도 그래야 할 것 같습니다.
I'll do it very quickly.
아주 빨리 할게요.
Ow, my stomach.
아, 배가.
That hurts!
그 상처!
Junmo.
준모.
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
I almost died.
거의 죽을 뻔 했어.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
It's ok.
괜찮아요.
Gicheul actually seems to be smuggling when he goes fishing.
기철이는 사실 낚시하러 갈 때 밀수를 하는 것 같아요.
And tonight
그리고 오늘 밤
he wants to kill the gang's traitor.
그는 갱단의 반역자를 죽이고 싶어합니다.
We have to prevent that.
우리는 그것을 막아야 합니다.
OK. Take care.
좋아요. 잘 지내세요.
I'll do it.
나는 그것을 할 거 야.
INCOMING CALL
수신 전화
Hallo?
어이?
Incheon port in two days?
이틀만에 인천항?
Are you coming here?
여기 오시나요?
In order.
순서대로.
I'll make the salutation easier for you.
인사말을 더 쉽게 할게요.
Seungho is the oldest here,
여기서 승호가 가장 나이가 많고,
From now on you will call him "Sir".
이제부터는 그를 '선생님'이라고 부르겠습니다.
Ok?
좋아요?
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
Louder, you bastards!
더 크게, 이 놈들아!
Yes, boss!
예 보스!
Do you know who sold us...
누가 우리를 팔았는지 아세요?
... to the Jaegeon group?
...재건그룹에?
Good to meet you.
당신을 만나서 좋은.
If you decline, someone else will accept our offer.
당신이 거절하면 다른 사람이 우리 제안을 받아들일 것입니다.
Think about it carefully.
신중하게 생각해보세요.
Look around
주위를 둘러보세요
and look who isn't here,
그리고 누가 여기 없는지 보세요.
because they don't want to die.
왜냐하면 그들은 죽고 싶지 않기 때문입니다.
Kyungjin, Byungwoo und Chief Seo.
Kyungjin, Byungwoo und Chief Seo.
I don't see the three.
셋이 안보이네요
Sorry. I couldn't get a taxi.
죄송합니다. 택시를 탈 수가 없었어요.
Who is the traitor?
배신자는 누구입니까?
I think not Heesung or Jungbae.
희성이나 정배는 아닌 것 같아요 .
They're all alive, don't worry.
다들 살아 있으니 걱정하지 마세요.
Oh Kyungjin.
오경진.
We should find him and get him away quickly.
그를 찾아서 빨리 데려가야 합니다 .
He was the only one who knew the situation in the Jaegeon group.
재건 일행의 상황을 아는 유일한 사람이었다 .
Oh Kyungjin.
오경진.
Hallo?
어이?
Kyungjin?
경진?
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
Oh Kyungjin.
오경진.
Oh Kyungjin!
오경진!
Damned.
저주 받은.
Fuck.
못쓰게 만들다.
Fuck ...
젠장 ...
Kyungjin, why did you do it?
경진아, 왜 그랬어?
Why are you asking me this?
왜 나한테 이런 걸 묻는 거야?
It's shameful for me.
나로서는 부끄러운 일이다.
Yeah, that's not important, is it?
응, 그건 중요하지 않지, 그렇지?
What matters is you caused this mess.
중요한 것은 당신이 이 혼란을 야기했다는 것입니다.
I want you to see
꼭 보셨으면 좋겠어요
what happens when you cheat on your family.
가족을 속이면 어떻게 되나요 ?
Chief Seo.
서 실장님.
Fuck.
못쓰게 만들다.
Boss.
사장.
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
What are you planning to do now?
지금은 무엇을 할 계획인가요?
That bastard almost cost you your life.
그 놈은 거의 목숨을 잃을 뻔했어요.
He has to pay for that.
그는 그 비용을 지불해야 합니다.
Try to endure it.
그것을 견뎌보십시오.
Because it will hurt.
상처를 입을 것이기 때문입니다.
You fucking son of a bitch.
이 빌어먹을 개자식아.
Let's see it.
어디 보자.
Damn son of a bitch. Mieses Dreckschwein.
빌어먹을 개자식. 미제스 드렉슈바인.
Damn sneaky rat.
빌어먹을 교활한 쥐새끼.
Stupid trash bag.
멍청한 쓰레기봉투.
Damn son of a bitch.
빌어먹을 개자식.
You piece of shit.
이 똥같은 놈아.
I almost died because of you, you fucker.
너 때문에 죽을 뻔했어, 이 새끼야.
OK? Fucking traitor.
좋아요? 빌어먹을 배신자.
Boss.
사장.
That should be enough for him almost killing me.
그 사람이 나를 거의 죽일 뻔 했다면 그것만으로도 충분할 것입니다 .
-Hey, Yongdae. -Ja, Sir.
-안녕 용대야. - 예, 선생님.
Stay out of my sight.
내 눈에 띄지 마세요.
If I see you again, I'll kill you.
다시 만나면 죽여버릴 거야.
Heesung, Jungbae, Chief Seo, follow me.
희성, 정배, 서과장님 따라오세요.
You too, Seungho.
너도 승호야.
Consider yourself lucky, you bastard.
운이 좋다고 생각해라, 이 개자식아.
Clean up here.
여기서 청소하세요.
Yes, Sir!
알겠습니다!
Throw him far away.
그를 멀리 던져라.
Yes, Sir.
알겠습니다.
The Chinese are coming in two days.
중국인들이 이틀 뒤에 온다.
Why all of a sudden?
왜 갑자기?
Why don't we talk about this more privately, sir?
이 문제에 대해 좀 더 개인적으로 이야기해 볼까요 ?
No, we need more than just the three of us now.
아니요, 지금은 우리 셋보다 더 많은 것이 필요합니다.
You already know what's going on, right?
무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 이미 알고 계시죠?
I'll take care of her.
내가 그녀를 돌볼께.
Prepare something that will brighten her mood.
그녀의 기분을 밝게 해줄 무언가를 준비하십시오 .
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
And Heesung,
그리고 희성님,
find out if Kyungjin is up to something.
경진이가 뭔가 꾸미고 있는지 알아보세요.
Ok.
좋아요.
Seo, take care of Seungho.
서 씨, 승호를 잘 돌봐주세요.
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
You can go.
당신은 갈 수 있습니다.
HIDEOUT IN DONGHOBANG CHINA
중국 동호방의 은신처
SEOUL, DISTRICT ATTORNEY OF SOUTH KOREA
서울, 대한민국 지방검사
DRUG MANUFACTURERS CONVICTED DRUG OFFENDERS
마약 제조업체에서 마약 범죄자로 유죄 판결을 받은 사람
Among those convicted of meth
마약으로 유죄 판결을 받은 사람들 중
we examined all the meth cooks.
우리는 모든 마약 요리사를 조사했습니다.
YOON WONGIL
윤원일
Yoon Wongil.
윤원길.
Why did she still go to China?
그녀는 왜 아직도 중국에 갔는가?
To travel.
여행하다.
She's not back?
그 사람이 돌아오지 않았나요?
No.
아니요.
Traveling in China for half a year?
반년 동안 중국을 여행하시나요?
Get the interpreter.
통역사를 구하세요.
Ich rufe Mr. Murayama an.
Ich rufe Mr. Murayama an.
Yes, Sir.
알겠습니다.
-Captain Seok? -Hallo, Sir.
- 석 선장님? -안녕하세요, 선생님.
Do you know Professor Yoon?
윤 교수님을 아시나요?
Die grauhaarige Dame.
Grauhaarige Dame을 죽어라.
I have something big here.
여기에 뭔가 큰 것이 있습니다.
This trade could not only Korea and Japan,
이번 무역은 한국과 일본뿐만 아니라,
but affect Korea, China and Japan.
그러나 한국, 중국, 일본에 영향을 미칩니다.
The Chinese are now among our suspects.
이제 중국인도 우리의 용의자 중 하나입니다.
If Detective Park attends the meeting with the Chinese tomorrow,
박형사가 내일 중국인과의 면담에 참석한다면,
we can better evaluate this theory .
우리는 이 이론을 더 잘 평가할 수 있습니다.
Do we ask him for help?
그에게 도움을 요청하나요?
NATIONAL DRUG COMMISSIONER BEIJING, CHINA
중국 국가약품감독관 베이징
WANTED YOON WONGIL, KOREAN, 73
수배 윤원일, 한국인, 73세
Hallo?
어이?
Hi, Gicheul. It's me, Euijeong.
안녕, 기철아. 나야, 의정.
Hi, Euijeong.
안녕하세요, 의정님.
I should have called you.
내가 너한테 전화했어야 했는데.
How are you doing? Are you OK?
어떻게 지내세요? 괜찮으세요?
Yes, thank you.
네 감사합니다.
Thank you for coming to the funeral.
장례식에 와주셔서 감사합니다 .
You don't have to thank me, that was my duty.
나한테 고마워할 필요는 없어. 그건 내 의무였어.
Speaking of which,
말하자면,
are you free tomorrow?
내일 시간있어?
Morning?
아침?
Yes, tomorrow is the only day I have free.
응, 내일은 내가 시간이 있는 유일한 날이야 .
Can we meet?
우리 만날 수 있나요?
Yes that works. Let's meet tomorrow.
네, 작동합니다. 내일 만나자.
Say Seungho please
승호라고 말해주세요
that I would also like to thank him for his visit.
그의 방문에 대해서도 감사의 말씀을 전하고 싶습니다 .
I will do.
내가 할 것이다.
I have an important appointment tomorrow.
내일 중요한 약속이 있어요.
You take care of the Chinese.
당신은 중국인을 돌봐주세요.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
Have you checked hospitals?
병원을 확인해 보셨나요?
Boss.
사장.
Can I answer that with Chief Seo?
서과장님한테 대답해도 될까요 ?
Finish eating first.
먼저 식사를 마치세요.
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
Heesung.
희성.
What's your baby's name?
아기의 이름은 무엇입니까?
Jaeyoung.
재영.
Hong Jaeyoung.
홍재영.
That's a great name.
정말 좋은 이름이군요.
I'm coming to visit.
나는 방문하러 간다.
Secure. The baby is so sweet.
안전한. 아기가 너무 귀엽습니다.
Doesn't look like me at all.
전혀 나처럼 보이지 않습니다.
It looks like Hyeok.
혁이 닮았네요.
What did you want to say in confidence?
자신 있게 무슨 말을 하고 싶었나요?
Chief Seo.
서 실장님.
You investigated where Oh Kyungjin was that day, right?
그날 오경진이 어디 있는지 조사했지 ?
Naturally.
당연히.
I'm just wondering
그냥 궁금해서요
how to locate our car
우리 차 찾는 방법
and could inform them.
그리고 그들에게 알릴 수 있었습니다.
He didn't chase our car.
그 사람은 우리 차를 쫓지 않았어요.
Jungbae followed us that day.
그날도 정배가 따라왔다.
Do you suspect Jungbae?
정배를 의심하시나요?
You too, Chief Seo?
서과장님도요?
Yes, I have that suspicion too.
네, 저도 그런 의심을 갖고 있어요.
Boss.
사장.
Let's do one final check.
마지막으로 한 번 확인해 보겠습니다.
Our guests from China
중국에서 온 손님
seem important to our business.
우리 사업에 중요한 것 같아요 .
How about sending Seungho while I check on Jungbae?
내가 정배를 확인하는 동안 승호를 보내는 건 어때 ?
You should be careful
너 조심하는 게 좋아
until we are sure about Jungbae and Heesung.
정배와 희성에 대해 확신할 때까지 .
Jungbae is like my little brother.
정배는 내 동생 같은 존재다.
Do it professionally.
전문적으로 수행하십시오.
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
Chief Seo.
서 실장님.
You can leave. Do it right.
떠날 수 있습니다. 올바르게 하세요.
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
Hallo, Boss.
안녕하세요, 보스.
You have the information on all of my people, right?
당신은 내 사람들 전체에 대한 정보를 갖고 있죠 ?
Yes, I have.
네, 있어요.
I need to do some research.
조사를 좀 해야 해요 .
If everything goes right,
모든 일이 제대로 진행된다면,
The old goes out and the new comes in.
오래된 것은 사라지고 새로운 것이 들어옵니다.
You called, sir?
전화했어요 선생님?
Do you have any gifts for the Chinese?
중국인에게 줄 선물이 있나요?
Yes, I have something expensive ready.
응, 비싼 걸 준비했어.
Good job.
잘했어요.
Thanks, boss.
고마워요, 보스.
Also ...
또한 ...
... I would like to drink something,
... 뭔가 마시고 싶은데,
but I don't want to drink alone.
하지만 나는 혼자 술을 마시고 싶지 않아요.
And.
그리고.
Great. I was just about to grab a drink myself.
엄청난. 나도 막 혼자 술 한잔 마시려고 하던 참이었다 .
Should I prepare the drinks outside?
음료수는 밖에서 준비해야 하나요?
Sounds good.
좋은 것 같아요.
Ok, Sir.
알겠습니다.
PATROL PROTOCOL
순찰 프로토콜
Sir.
선생님.
Sir?
선생님?
A simple survey.
간단한 설문조사입니다.
You can answer my questions with a nod.
제 질문에 고개를 끄덕이시면 대답 하실 수 있습니다 .
Our investigation is stuck here.
우리 조사가 여기서 막혔어요.
How did you know which route Jung Gicheul would take?
정기철이 어느 길로 갈지 어떻게 알았나요 ?
Did someone track his car and tell them?
누군가 그의 차를 추적해서 알려줬나요?
Then how did you know?
그럼 어떻게 알았어?
Did your gang follow his car,
당신네 친구들이 그 사람 차를 따라갔나요?
all the way from Seoul?
서울에서 줄곧?
With the car you were in?
당신이 타고 있던 차를 가지고요?
Aber Sir, ...
애버 선생님, ...
... You were shot,
... 당신은 총에 맞았습니다.
but that you don't recognize my face?
그런데 당신이 내 얼굴을 모른다고?
I'm Seo Jongryeol.
저는 서종렬이에요.
Nice to talk to you alone,
혼자 얘기해서 반가워요
without the other boys.
다른 소년들 없이.
It's been a while.
오랜만이야.
Please.
제발.
And.
그리고.
I'm sending Kwon Seungho
권승호 보내요
tomorrow morning to Icheon port.
내일 아침 이천항으로.
Get some rest.
좀 쉬.
Yes, Boss.
예 보스.
That's life.
인생이 다 그렇지.
It always gets you in the end.
그것은 항상 결국 당신을 데려옵니다.
Take it like that.
그렇게 받아들이십시오.
And this,
이,
like sinking into peaceful sleep.
평화로운 잠에 빠지는 것처럼.
Since you bring it up...
그걸 올리시니까...
Also ...
또한 ...
Just in case...
만약을 대비해서...
Just to be sure,
확인차,
You didn't suspect me or Heesung, did you?
나나 희성도 의심 하지 않았지 ?
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Correct.
옳은.
Sorry. Forget it, boss.
죄송합니다. 잊어버리세요, 보스.
Hallo?
어이?
Boss, this is Jongryeol.
사장님, 종렬이에요.
As per your instruction
귀하의 지시에 따라
I killed Kang Geon.
내가 강건을 죽였어.
Heesung and Jungbae...
희성과 정배..
...they are clean.
...깨끗해요.
Well done. Take a break.
잘하셨어요. 휴식을 취하다.
Who was that, boss?
저 사람은 누구였나요, 보스?
Nobody.
아무도.
Prost.
프로스트.
If you think about it...
생각해보면...
Yes, Boss?
예 보스?
You and me. We were always together, right?
너와 나. 우리는 늘 함께였죠?
Don't we both know that for sure, boss?
우리 둘 다 그걸 확실히 알고 있지 않습니까, 보스?
Son of pre-school stationer, Choi Jungbae.
유치원교사 최정배 의 아들 .
Why are you talking about the old days? It is strange.
왜 옛날 이야기를 하는 걸까요? 그것은 이상해.
Are you drunk?
취했나요?
As the only student
유일한 학생으로서
Yeoksam High
역삼고
Did you have an apartment?
아파트가 있었나요?
I was the only one living in half a basement.
나는 지하 반층에 사는 유일한 사람이었습니다 .
The poor.
가난한.
Since it's just the two of us here,
여기엔 우리 둘 뿐이니까,
do not meet with the Chinese yourself,
중국인을 직접 만나지 마세요 .
because there is something important?
중요한 일이 있어서?
There is nothing.
아무것도 없습니다.
Boss, like you said,
사장님 말씀대로
I have accompanied you all my life.
나는 평생 동안 당신과 동행했습니다.
I can read your mind pretty well.
나는 당신의 마음을 꽤 잘 읽을 수 있습니다.
Is it because of that woman, Yu Euijeong?
그 여자 유의정 때문인가 ?
-Jungbae. -Ja, Boss?
-정배. - 예, 보스?
If you can read my mind,
내 마음을 읽을 수 있다면,
you should be able to look away too .
당신도 멀리 볼 수 있어야합니다 .
You're right. But it doesn't make any sense.
네가 옳아. 그러나 그것은 아무런 의미가 없습니다.
You can't marry a police officer.
경찰관과 결혼할 수는 없습니다.
I can not?
나는 할 수 없다?
Please?
제발?
They marry?
결혼해요?
Oh.
오.
Honestly, I'm a little scared.
솔직히 좀 겁이 나네요.
What if something bad happens because of her?
그녀 때문에 나쁜 일이 생기면 어쩌지 ?
I just want you to be clear
난 그냥 네가 명확해지길 바래
that you are starting something very dangerous.
당신이 매우 위험한 일을 시작하고 있다는 것입니다.
Some things are dangerous
어떤 것들은 위험해요
but worth a try, right?
하지만 시도해 볼 가치가 있지, 그렇지?
And.
그리고.
True.
진실.
Let's drink to that.
그걸로 마시자.
Hey.
여기요.
How are you?
어떻게 지내세요?
Choi Jungbae.
최정배.
And, Sir?
그리고 선생님?
Do you trust me?
당신은 날 믿어?
I trust them.
나는 그들을 신뢰합니다.
I trust you too.
나도 당신을 믿습니다.
Jung Gicheul is starting to trust me.
정기철이가 나를 믿기 시작했다.
From now on, whenever I'm free...
이제부터 시간 날 때마다...
Stop. Let's not talk about it now.
멈추다. 지금은 그것에 대해 이야기하지 말자 .
I don't want to think about it.
나는 그것에 대해 생각하고 싶지 않습니다.
Ok.
좋아요.
I just want to think about us.
나는 단지 우리에 대해 생각하고 싶습니다.
Correct.
옳은.
Your mother.
당신의 어머니.
Was the funeral okay?
장례식은 괜찮았나요?
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
And your injury?
부상은요?
Are you all right?
괜찮으세요?
Yes I'm fine.
네, 저는 괜찮아요.
Eat up.
먹어라.
You asshole.
이 멍청아.
You're distracting me, you asshole.
넌 내 주의를 산만하게 하고 있어, 이 멍청아.
Think about it.
생각해 보세요.
Don’t you think Gicheul trusts Seungho too much?
기철이가 승호를 너무 믿는 것 같지 않나요 ?
What's wrong now?
지금 무슨 문제가 있나요?
Does it bother me that he sent it?
그 사람이 보낸 게 귀찮나요?
to the important meeting, and not us.
우리가 아니라 중요한 회의에 .
But you have a little free time.
하지만 약간의 자유 시간이 있습니다.
When he said "important appointment"
중요한 약속이라고 했을 때
Did he mean a date with the policewoman, you know?
그 사람이 여경이랑 데이트하자는 뜻이었나요 ?
However, that bothers me too.
하지만 그게 나도 귀찮다.
Or?
또는?
Doesn't matter. It's his business.
상관없어요. 그것은 그의 사업입니다.
Let's take care of ours.
우리를 돌보자.
Yoon Wongil. Did time for meth and went to China.
윤원길. 마약을 마실 시간을 갖고 중국으로 갔다.
Check if she is this Chinese guest.
그 사람 이 중국인 손님 인지 확인해 보세요 .
INCHEON PASSAGIER-TERMINAL
인천여객터미널
Dear passengers...
친애하는 승객 여러분...
Are you from Mr. Jung?
정씨 출신이신가요?
Yes that's me.
그래 그게 나야.
Let's go.
갑시다.
I said somewhere nice.
나는 어딘가 좋은 곳이라고 말했다.
I wanted to visit the church. It is a long time ago.
나는 교회를 방문하고 싶었습니다. 오래전 일이다.
Is that ok?
그 확인은?
Naturally.
당연히.
It would be nice,
그것은 좋은 것입니다,
when your mother went to church again.
네 엄마가 다시 교회에 갔을 때.
As far as I know,
내가 아는 한,
if you are from China,
당신이 중국 출신이라면,
Only Korean Chinese over 55 can enter Korea.
55세 이상의 조선족만 한국에 입국할 수 있습니다.
That's why I did n't expect anyone so young.
그렇기 때문에 이렇게 어린 사람이 나올 거라고는 예상하지 못했습니다.
We don't do something like this unprepared.
우리는 준비 없이 이런 일을 하지 않습니다.
I wasn't expecting a Korean woman.
한국 여자를 기대한 건 아니었어요.
I am Korean-Chinese.
저는 조선족입니다.
And I didn't expect someone so naive.
그리고 나는 그렇게 순진한 사람을 기대하지 않았습니다 .
Does the person you came with take a taxi?
같이 온 사람이 택시를 타나요 ?
Because of the recent breakdown...
최근 고장으로 인해..
I would like to apologize.
사과드리고 싶습니다.
We are very sorry.
우리는 매우 유감 스럽습니다.
Is this typical Korea?
이게 전형적인 한국인가요?
let others apologize for you?
다른 사람들이 당신을 위해 사과하도록 하시겠습니까 ?
One makes a mistake,
한 사람은 실수를 하고,
the other apologizes.
다른 하나는 사과합니다.
Very interesting.
매우 흥미로운.
Get some rest.
좀 쉬.
Your name?
당신의 이름?
I'm Kwon Seungho.
저는 권승호입니다.
They are Korean Chinese.
그들은 조선족 중국인입니다.
Their passports must be fake, investigations are pointless.
여권은 위조된 게 틀림없어 조사는 의미가 없다.
I wonder why they came to Korea.
그들이 한국에 왜 왔는지 궁금해요 .
To hand the material over to land now ?
지금 땅에 물질을 넘겨주려면?
Customs in Incheon would not be easy to get through.
인천 세관 통과가 쉽지 않을 것 같아요.
It has to be something else.
그것은 다른 것이어야 합니다.
Let's watch them.
그들을 지켜보자.
What are you actually doing here?
당신은 실제로 여기서 무엇을 하고 있는 걸까요?
Shouldn't you be with Gicheul?
기철이랑 같이 있으면 안되는 걸까?
I'll do this here.
여기서 할게요.
Jung Gicheul is currently
정기철은 현재
with Inspector Yu.
유 검사관과 함께.
Why is Euijeong meeting him?
의정이 그 사람을 왜 만나요?
Didn't you see what the bastard did at the funeral?
그 새끼가 장례식에서 뭘 했는지 못 봤어 ?
Since you were injured, she wanted to help us.
당신이 부상을 당했기 때문에 그녀는 우리를 돕고 싶어했습니다.
Why ...
왜 ...
Why is Euijeong helping us now?
의정이 지금 우리를 돕는 이유는 무엇인가요?
Damn, I should be faced with such a decision
젠장, 나도 그런 결정을 내려야 해
not be asked first?
먼저 물어보지 말라고?
It was urgent, there was no time for it.
급한 일이라 시간이 없었습니다.
We couldn't just watch.
우리는 보고만 있을 수 없었습니다.
-Inspector You see it well too. -Verdammt.
- 조사님도 잘 보셨죠. -Verdammmt.
She insisted on doing everything she could to help you.
그녀는 당신을 돕기 위해 최선을 다하겠다고 고집했습니다 .
You trust her, don't you?
당신은 그녀를 믿죠, 그렇죠?
Don't think too much about it.
그것에 대해 너무 많이 생각하지 마십시오.
Thanks to her, these are potential Chinese drug producers
그녀 덕분에 이들은 잠재적인 중국 마약 생산자 들이다.
right before our eyes.
바로 우리 눈앞에서.
Damned.
저주 받은.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Subtitles by: Ingo Krallmann
자막: Ingo Krallmann